I: Do you have more free time than three years ago?
K: I actually definitely do have more free time than I did a couple of years ago,
as I actually just graduated from college.
This is my first year working full time, so working nine to five frees up your evenings,
so definitely more free time than before.
I: What’s the most beautiful city you’ve ever been to?
S: That’s such a good question.
Um, I think probably Athens.
I: Why?
S: It’s, it’s just, it’s absolutely gorgeous there – the Acropolis,
the Parthenon, the sights are beautiful.
Yeah, it’s the best place to go.
I: What do you drink in a typical day?
A: In a typical day I usually just drink,
er, a lot of coffee and water, sometimes juice.
I: Is there anything you drink too much of?
A: I probably drink too much coffee.
I: Is there anything you don’t drink enough of?
A: I don’t drink enough water most days,
but I’m trying to get better.
I: Are you an optimist or a pessimist?
C: I am a realist.
Um, yeah, more pessimistic than optimistic.
I: Do you often dream about the same thing?
P: Yes, I do.
I had a really, really awful teacher at high school for history,
and she was always really mean.
And when I finished high school, I always dreamed that she would say,
‘You will never pass your A levels’.
And now I always dream of the same teacher from high school telling me,
‘You will never finish your degree,’
so that’s kind of weird, yeah.